{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516396190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516396189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516396570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516396570"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516397060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516397060"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516397413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516397412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516397825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516397825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516398311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516398310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516398544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516398543"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516401712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516401711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516401752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516401752"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516402470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516402470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516402863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516402863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516403156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516403156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516403359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516403359"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516403560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516403559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516403886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516403886"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516404116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516404116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516407347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516407347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516407751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516407751"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516410330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516410330"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516410533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516410533"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516410736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516410736"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516414241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516414240"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516417959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516417959"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516418981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516418981"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516421694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516421693"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516422068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516422068"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516422552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516422552"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516422895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516422895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516423299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516423299"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516423772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516423772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516423995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516423995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516427191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516427191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516427223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516427223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516427936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516427936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516428329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516428329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516428622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516428622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516428826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516428826"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516429020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516429020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516429333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516429333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516429556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516429556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516432257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516432257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516432321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516432321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" a3c54e87-126c-40bd-978f-f919b96476c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516445095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516445095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516445619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516445619"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516445872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516445872"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516446495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516446495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516449313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516449313"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516450087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516450087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516451130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516451130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516451723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516451722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516451735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516451735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516452398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516452398"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516453451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516453451"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516454115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516454115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516457090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516457090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516458063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516458062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516458516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516458516"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516459109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516459109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516459642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516459642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516460245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516460245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516463356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516463356"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516464268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516464268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516465441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516465441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TUNAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516466244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516466244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516469066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516469066"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516469599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516469599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516470153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516470152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516470616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516470615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516471498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516471498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516474512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516474512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516475705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516475704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516476337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516476337"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516480229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516480229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516481042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516481042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516481475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516481474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516483067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516483067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" ANATUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516486381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516486381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" ANATUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516487355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516487355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516488567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516488567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516491393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516491393"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516491935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516491935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516492779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516492779"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516493572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516493572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516493675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516493675"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516494518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516494518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516495281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516495281"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516496565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516496565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUNINUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516497288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516497288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516497593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516497593"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516498476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516498476"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516501282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516501282"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516502166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516502166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516502950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516502950"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516503783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516503783"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516506664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516506664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516508306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516508306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFAHAMU"," userResponse":" UMEFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516508610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516508610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516509173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516509173"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516510316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516510316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516510809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516510809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516510818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516510818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516511261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516511261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516511985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516511985"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516514651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516514650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516514718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516514717"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" f8b8594f-93b2-4915-bcab-1113ecf64323"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516530107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516530106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516530629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516530629"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516530882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516530882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516531504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516531504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516534305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516534305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516535078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516535078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516536121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516536121"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMFUGA"," userResponse":" AMEMFUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516536715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516536714"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516536727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516536727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516537404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516537403"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516538469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516538468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEITWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516539133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516539133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516542130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516542129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516543102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516543102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516543555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516543555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516544167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516544167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516544700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516544700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516545317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516545316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516548502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516548502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516549415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516549415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516550595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516550594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMPA"," userResponse":" TUNAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516551408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516551408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516554273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516554272"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516554814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516554814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516555380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516555379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516555856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516555856"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516556749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516556748"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo pia hunywa maji mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516559843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516559843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516561052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516561051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516561686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516561686"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninampenda Pendo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516565649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516565648"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMTUNZA"," userResponse":" TUNAMTUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516566476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516566475"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516566919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516566919"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516568519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516568519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunamtunza Pendo na anatusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" ANATUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516571918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516571918"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATUPA"," userResponse":" ANATUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516572903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516572903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516574127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516574126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatupa maziwa mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516576999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516576999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516577550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516577550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516578414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516578413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUUZA"," userResponse":" HUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516579223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516579220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516579327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516579327"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516580171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516580171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516580950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516580949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516582233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516582233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNINUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUNINUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516582956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516582956"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516583260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516583260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516584143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516584143"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu huuza baadhi ya maziwa na kuninunulia vitabu vya hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516586953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516586953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516587836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516587836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516588618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516588618"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516589461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516589461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma hadithi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516592394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516592393"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516594052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516594052"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFAHAMU"," userResponse":" UMEFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516594363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516594363"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516594939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516594939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516596094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516596094"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516596599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516596598"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516596615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516596615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516597059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516597059"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516597782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516597782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516600483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516600482"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516600580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516600579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 743a7cf0-eaf9-4a26-9f7d-22f890ab8e3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516623101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516623101"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-B"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516628520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516628520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-B"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516633599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516633599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-G-D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516639420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516639420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-CH-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516651966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516651966"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_V-F-E"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516655308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516655308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_R-N-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516660651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516660651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_R-N-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516666130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516666130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_CH-F-K"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516671808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516671808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_L-F-Z"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516677101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516677101"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-U-J"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516682130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516682130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-O-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516687388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516687388"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-A-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516691238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516691237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" eaee4fdc-38d8-4901-af1e-8a488dc5709e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_F-A-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516701606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516701606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516703376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516703376"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516705462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516705462"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516707423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516707422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516708700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516708700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516710491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516710490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516713247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516713247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516714973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516714972"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516716730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516716730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516718503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516718503"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516720492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516720492"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516722402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516722402"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516726113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516726113"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516726749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516726749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516727934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516727934"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516729525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516729525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516729636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516729636"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" d7f820f3-aadb-42bd-aea9-e06897310168"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516741695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516741695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516743464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516743464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516752834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516752833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516754781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516754781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516755913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516755912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516757681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516757681"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516758964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516758964"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516760684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516760684"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516762908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516762908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516764848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516764847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516767040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516767040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516768826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516768826"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516772339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516772339"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516772526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516772525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ae696906-0b3e-4d0f-a1ec-0762a20a9f8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516781881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516781881"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ea597f2a-da3a-4665-9086-bf8f8d4d51db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516782888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516782887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ea597f2a-da3a-4665-9086-bf8f8d4d51db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516782973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516782973"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" ea597f2a-da3a-4665-9086-bf8f8d4d51db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516792261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516792260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516792844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516792844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516793511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516793510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516793659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516793659"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516794046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516794046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516794450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516794450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516795565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516795564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516796559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516796559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516797123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516797123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516797286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516797286"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516798098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516798098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516801026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516801025"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516802050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516802050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516803074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516803074"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516804141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516804141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" IKIENDESHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516805374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516805374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEREMKA"," userResponse":" KUTEREMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516805958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516805958"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516808814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516808813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516809304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516809304"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516810135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516810134"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516811398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516811397"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" LIKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516812257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516812256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516812469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516812469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516813124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516813123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516813540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516813539"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516814263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516814263"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516814557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516814557"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516815350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516815350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516818381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516818380"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516818559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516818558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516819088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516819088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516819762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516819761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516821151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516821150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516821747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516821747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516822231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516822231"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516822454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516822454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516823207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516823207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNUNU"," userResponse":" RUNUNU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516825931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516825931"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516827115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516827114"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" AKIZINGATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516827928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516827927"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516831463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516831463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516832662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516832662"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGONGA"," userResponse":" LILIGONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516833010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516833010"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516836359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516836359"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516836443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516836443"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516837580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516837579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516838456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516838456"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516838668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516838667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516839601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516839601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516841044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516841044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516842042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516842041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" KUTOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516843455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516843455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516847015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516847014"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516847879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516847879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516847984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516847984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516848639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516848638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" KUVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516849482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516849482"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516850535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516850535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIFIKA"," userResponse":" YALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516853006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516853006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516853909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516853908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIVUTA"," userResponse":" LILIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516854412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516854412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516857043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516857042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516857997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516857996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAVUTA"," userResponse":" LIKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516858400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516858400"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516861749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516861749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516862182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516862182"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516862745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516862744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516865949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516865948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULITISHIKA"," userResponse":" TULITISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516866467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516866467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516869254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516869252"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516869344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516869344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516876288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516876288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_DES.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516883616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516883616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 27be743b-0e13-4c6e-b452-82db8e70e71f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516901693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516901692"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 2cec8f2e-81ac-4af6-b7ff-522d1b9ece64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516907880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516907879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 2cec8f2e-81ac-4af6-b7ff-522d1b9ece64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516938450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516938449"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 2cec8f2e-81ac-4af6-b7ff-522d1b9ece64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516938522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516938521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 46de94f1-8871-4d01-ad39-61b1bb64162d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516946907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516946907"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 46de94f1-8871-4d01-ad39-61b1bb64162d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516960008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516960008"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 46de94f1-8871-4d01-ad39-61b1bb64162d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548516971732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548516971732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 46de94f1-8871-4d01-ad39-61b1bb64162d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517014362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517014362"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 46de94f1-8871-4d01-ad39-61b1bb64162d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Pendo anapenda kula nyasi siku nzima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517014445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517014445"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 16cd6174-7622-4b2b-b8f7-2b3bece32da4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517067823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517067823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 16cd6174-7622-4b2b-b8f7-2b3bece32da4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ekeno alionywa na wazazi asiingie msituni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517067886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517067885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 8b53bce4-8e87-4888-a0d9-0dad103bfd7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517161260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517161260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 8b53bce4-8e87-4888-a0d9-0dad103bfd7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Ekeno alipuuza ushauri wa wazazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548517161335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548517161335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_182623"," gameId":" 8c1597c1-9cbe-4dc0-81c1-5a74dcc2b3a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}